Athletics, Department of; Records ua746
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Photographs, 9; 14.86 cubic ft.
  - New York Giants Totaro, 1999 August 4 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Unidentified Female Soccer Player, 1999 September (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Baseball, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Baseball Mike Kuebler, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Columbia Basketball Pre - Game Alumni Party, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Field Hockey, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Field Hockey Proofs, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Football, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Football, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Football, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Football, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Football Proofs, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Giants [cd], 2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Lacrosse [3.5 in floppy], 2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Men's Soccer, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Men's Soccer, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Men's Soccer Proofs, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Softball, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Women's Field Hockey, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Women's Field Hockey Players, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Women's Lacrosse, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Women's Soccer, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Women's Soccer Proofs, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Volleyball, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Football Negatives, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Athletics [ 3.5 in floppy], 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Basketball Negatives, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Headshots, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Women's Basketball, Part 1, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Women's Basketball, Part 2, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Headshots - Men's Lacrosse, ca. 2005 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Headshots - Women's Lacrosse, ca. 2000s (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Lee McElloy, ca. 2000s (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Men's Track, ca. 2000s (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Opponents, ca. 2000s (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Women's Basketball Headshots, ca. 2000s (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Women's Soccer, Fall 2000 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Brian DePasquale Asst. Director for Media Relations - Athletic Inserts, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Field Hockey Headshots with Negatives, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Football [cd], 2001 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Football Headshots, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country [cd], 2001 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Men's Basketball - purple growl, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Softball, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Track and Field Negative [cd], 2001 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Volleyball [cd], 2001 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Volleyball Headshots, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - women's soccer [cd], 2001 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Field Hockey [cd], 2001 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Baseball Headshots, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Headshots, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball [cd], 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Men's Lacrosse Headshots, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Track and Field Headshots, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Softball Headshots, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Women's Basketball Headshots, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Women's Lacrosse Headshots, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Men's Basketball Headshots, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Football Team Photos, 2001-2011 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - 2001 Giants Training Camp, Photographed by Mike Totaro, 2001 August 1
  - Athletic Hall of Fame Headshots, Meredith Jackel, Blake Kim, Cort Kim, Tonya Dodge, Rudy Vido, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Field Hockey, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Field Hockey [CD], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Football, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Football Headshots, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Football - Team photo and same, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Football vs Central Conn. [cd], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Giants Camp, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Great Danes Awards and Dinner Digital, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country [cd], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Men's Lacrosse, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Men's Lacrosse [cd], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Men's Soccer [cd], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Men's Soccer [cd], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Softball [cd], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Track [cd], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Volleyball [cd], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Women's Basketball, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Women's Lacrosse [cd], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Women's Soccer [cd], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Women's Golf [cd], 2002 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Men's and Women's Growl [cd], 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Men's Basketball [cd], 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Great Danes Logos, 2002 May 28
  - Field Hockey Shots, 2002 October 1
  - Football Team and Schedule, 2003 (Oversized 1)
  - Media Guide Photos: Men's Soccer, 2003
  - Media Guide Photos: Library, 2003; 2007
  - Baseball [cd], 2003 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Field Hockey [cd], 2003 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Football [cd], 2003 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Football Team Photo, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country [cd], 2003 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Men's Lacrosse and Baseball, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Men's Lacrosse [cd], 2003 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Men's Soccer {cd}, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Original proofs - Football, Women's soccer, Men's soccer, Women's field hockey, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Softball, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Softball [cd], 2003 (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Track, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - USA Basketball Women's National Team, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Volleyball, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Volleyball [cd], 2003 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Volleyball [cd], 2003 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Winter/Spring Sport Headshots part 1, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Winter/Spring Sport Headshots part 2, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Women's Soccer, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Women's Tennis [cd], 2003 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Women's Lacrosse[cd], 2003 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Media Guide Photos: Classrooms, 2003-2004; 2010
  - Assorted Headshots [cd], 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Brian DePasquale, Spring Sports Headshots, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Football Game, 2003 Fall (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Giants, 2003 July 25
  - Giants Scrimmage, 2003 August 5
  - Men's Lacrosse at Hartford, 2004
  - Media Guide Photos: Residential Area, 2004; 2006
  - Football Proofs, 2004
  - Baseball, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Baseball [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Field Hockey [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Football staff, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Men's and Women's Soccer, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Men's Basketball [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Men's Basketball vs Siena [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Men's Soccer [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Orchard Park Gold Course [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Softball [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Track and field [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Volleyball [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Women's Basketball [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Women's Basketball, Liz/Dawn, Captain Negatives, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - (Redbone) Spring Invoice [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Women's Soccer [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Women's Soccer [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Women's Tennis [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Volleyball set up [cd], 2004 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball [cd], 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Men's Basketball, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Track and Field Team Photos [cd], 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Winter/Spring Sports [cd], 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Women's Basketball, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - 2004 UAlbany Athletics Logos, 2004 March
  - Men's Lacrosse at Hartford, Spring 2004 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Men's Lacrosse vs Binghamton, Spring 2004 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Athletics Logos, 2004 April 12
  - Men's Lacrosse at Hartford, Spring 2004, 2004 April 30
  - Great Dane Awards, 2004 May 4
  - Men's Lacrosse v. Binghamton, 2004 May 6
  - Men's Lacrosse Champions, 2004 June 2
  - Great Dane Awards (1 of 2), 2004 June 9
  - Great Dane Awards (2 of 2), 2004 June 9
  - Football vs. Monmouth, Fall 2004 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Football vs. St. Francis, Fall 2004 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Women's Golf, Fall 2004 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Giants and Jets Practice at Albany, 2004 August 7
  - Fall 2004 Golf Team, 2004 October 3
  - Football v. St. Francis, 2004 October 10
  - Football Action Shots, 2004 October 11
  - Hall of Fame, 2004 October 18
  - Women's Basketball Team Photos, 2004 November 1
  - Maine Black Bears Football Poster, 2005 (Oversized 1)
  - Football v. Sacred Heart, 2005
  - Baseball, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Baseball [CD], 2005 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Field Hockey, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Field Hockey [cd], 2005 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Football vs. Hofstra, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Football vs. Sacred Heart, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Men's and Women's Cross Country [cd], 2005 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Men's and Women's Headshots, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Men's and Women's Headshots, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Men and Women's Track A. East Champ [cd], 2005 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Men's Lacrosse vs Bingo, Softball [cd], 2005 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Men's Soccer, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Rich Schmitt Photography [cd], 2005 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Softball 2005 A - East Championship [cd] (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Volleyball, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Women's Lacrosse vs Siena, [cd], 2005 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Women's Soccer, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Women's Tennis, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Football vs. Stony Brook, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Women's Basketball
  - Men's Basketball, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Men's Basketball [cd], 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Women's Basketball [cd], 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Football Team Captains, ca. 2010s (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Women's Track and Field, Discus Throw, ca. 2010s (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Women's Track and Field, High Jum, ca. 2010s (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Men's Lacrosse v. Dartmouth, 2005 March 30
  - Men's Lacrosse vs. Dartmouth, Spring 2005 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Women's Golf, America East Tournament, Spring 2005 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Men's Lacrosse at Syracuse, 2005 April 22
  - Great Danes Awards [cd]/Lax Team Turf Fields, 2005 May 2; 2005 May 12; 2005 May 18 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Women's Golf, America East Tournament, 2005 May 3
  - Men's Lacrosse Championship v. Stony Brook, 2005 May 7
  - Great Dane Awards, 2005 May 10
  - Giants Media Day, 2005 July 28
  - Fall 2005 Team Photos, 2005 August 18
  - Football v. Hofstra, 2005 September 11
  - Fall 2005 Women's Golf, 2005 October 5
  - Women's Soccer, 2005 October 7
  - Fall 2005 Women's Soccer, 2005 October 7
  - Football v. Stony Brook, 2005 October 9
  - 2005 Men's Cross Country, 2005 October 16
  - 2005 Women's Cross Country, 2005 October 16
  - Football v. Sacred Heart, 2005 October 16
  - Women's Basketball Team, 2005 October 27
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Men's Cross Country, 2005 October 29
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Women's Cross Country, 2005 October 29
  - Posed Volleyball Shots, 2005 November 15
  - Men's Basketball v. Siena, 2005 December
  - Men's Basketball v. Binghamton, 2005 December 20
  - Big Purple Growl, 2006
  - Football v. Saint Francis, Homecoming, 2006
  - Baseball Pictures - with Disc, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Baseball [cds], 2006 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Men's and Women's Track and Field 2006 America East Conference Championships [cd] (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Softball [cd], 2006 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Women's lacrosse, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Football Team and Coaches, 2006; 2008 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - 2007-2008 UAlbany Player Photos, 2006-2008
  - Football Staff Photos, ca. 2001-2009 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Athlete Headshots, 2006 February 1
  - Men's Basketball v. Stony Brook, 2006 February 2
  - Women's Basketball v. Stony Brook, 2006 February 3
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Men's Basketball Awards, 2006 March 3
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Men's Basketball v. UMBC, 2006 March 4
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Men's Basketball v. UNH, 2006 March 5
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Men's Basketball v. UVM, 2006 March 5; 2006 March 13
  - Men's Basketball Championship, 2006 March 11
  - Spring 2006 Men's Lacrosse, 2006 April
  - Men's Lacrosse, Stony Brook and Binghamton, Spring 2006 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Softball, Spring 2006, 2006 April 12
  - Men's Lacrosse v. Binghamton with Field Dedication Ceremony, 2006 April 29-2006 April 30
  - Great Dane Awards, 2006 May
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Golf, 2006 May 2
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Golf Awards, 2006 May 2
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Track and Field Action Shots, 2006 May 7
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Track and Field Event Trophy, 2006 May 7
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Men's Lacrosse, 2006 May 7; 2006 May 11
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Track and Field Event, Saturday, 2006 May 13
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Track and Field Event, Sunday, 2006 May 13
  - 2005-2006 America East Championship: Softball, 2006 May 22
  - 2006 Softball Champions, 2006 May 24
  - America East Baseball Championship, Albany v. Vermont, 2006 May 25
  - America East Baseball Championship, Maine v. Stony Brook, 2006 May 25
  - America East Baseball Championship, Albany v. Stony Brook, 2006 May 26
  - Team Photos: Volleyball, Field Hockey, Women's Soccer, and Men's Soccer, 2006 August 18
  - Fall 2006 Volleyball v. Siena, 2006 September-2006 December
  - Fall 2006 Field Hockey, 2006 September 8
  - Football v. Fordham, 2006 September 9
  - Football Portraits, 2006 October 16
  - 2006 Hall of Fame, 2006 October 23
  - Football v. Wagner, 2006 October 28
  - Men's Basketball Ring Ceremony, 2006 November 11
  - Volleyball Action Shots, 2006 November 21
  - Baseball Pitchers, Spring 2007
  - Posed Track Shots, Spring 2007
  - Fall 2007 Cheer and Dance Team Photos
  - Football v. Sacred Heart, 2007
  - Fall 2007, Volleyball v. Brown
  - 2007 Big Purple Growl Fans, 2007 February
  - 2008 Big Purple Growl, Women's Basketball, 2007 February
  - 2007 Big Purple Growl, Men's Basketball, 2007 February
  - Men's Lacrosse v. Johns Hopkins, 2007 February-2007 March
  - Men's Lacrosse v. Johns Hopkins, 2007 February 24
  - Men's Basketball, America East Championship, 2007 March
  - America East Women's Basketball: Brunch, 2007 March
  - Men's Basketball v. UNH, America East Championship, 2007 March 6
  - Men's Basketball v. Boston, America East Championship, 2007 March 7
  - Women's Basketball v. Hartford, America East Championship, 2007 March 9
  - America East Women's Basketball Championship: Hartford Game, 2007 March 9
  - Women's Basketball v. UNH, America East Championship, 2007 March 12
  - Women's Lacrosse v. Siena, 2007 March 12
  - America East Women's Basketball Championship: UNH Game, 2007 March 12
  - Men's Lacrosse v. UMass, 2007 March 13
  - 2007 UAlbany Player Photos, 2007 April 10
  - Softball, America East Championship, 2007 May 13
  - Men's Lacrosse v. Loyola, 2007 May 13
  - Men's Basketball- NYS Assembly, 2007 May 14
  - Mara and Tisch Dedication Ceremony, 2007 August
  - Giants Training Camp (1 of 2), 2007 August 22
  - Giants Training Camp (2 of 2), 2007 August 22
  - Men's Soccer v. Syracuse, 2007 September 16
  - Hall of Fame Induction Ceremony, 2007 October 12
  - Hall of Fame, 2008
  - Volleyball, Women's Golf, Women's Field Hockey Champions, 2008; 2009 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Media Guide Photos: Campus Center and Bookstore, 2008-2010
  - Big Purple Growl Party, 2008 February
  - Big Purple Growl: Men's Basketball, 2008 February
  - Big Purple Growl: Women's Basketball, 2008 February
  - Softball v. Siena, 2008 April-2008 May
  - Softball v. Boston University, 2008 May 3
  - Men's Lacrosse Team Photos by Rob Totaro, 2008 May 6
  - Softball Team Photos by Rob Totaro, 2008 May 8
  - Giants Training Camp, 2008 July 28
  - Giants Training Camp, 2008 August 1
  - Giants Training Camp, 2008 August 3
  - Giants Training Camp, 2008 August 9
  - Rob Totaro Photography, Sports Portfolio, 2008 August 19
  - Men's Basketball: New Locker Rooms, 2008 October 8
  - Men's Basketball Team, 2008 October 8
  - Media Guide Photos: Indian Quad Dining Hall, 2009
  - Football Team, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Men's Indoor Track and Field Champions, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Men's Outdoor Track and Field Champions, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Great Dane Awards, 2009 May 11
  - Giants Training Camp, 2009 August 3
  - Giants Training Camp, 2009 August 7
  - Giants Training Camp, 2009 August 14
  - Giants Training Camp, 2009 August 24
  - Giants Training Camp, 2009 August 25
  - Football Team Photos, 2009 September 3
  - Hall of Fame, 2009 October 13
  - Photos for Virtual Guide, 2010
  - Women's Basketball, 2010; Undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Katie Abrahamson-Henderson, Head Women's Basketball Coach, 2010 April 20
  - 2009-2010 America East Championship, Track and Field, 2010 May 2
  - 2009-2010 America East Track and Field Championship, 2010 May 2
  - 2009-2010 America East Championship, Track and Field, 2010 May 2
  - Football North East Conference, 2011 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Great Dane Awards, 2011 May 5
  - Field Hockey Team Photos by Bill Ziskin, 2012
  - Men's Soccer Team Photos by Bill Ziskin, 2012
  - Women's Soccer Team Photos by Bill Ziskin, 2012
  - Headshots by Bill Ziskin, 2012 August 17
  - Headshots by Bill Ziskin, 2012 August 30
  - Headshots by Bill Ziskin, 2012 August 30
  - Bill Ziskin Photography, Headshots, 2013 February
  - Athletic Collages, 2013 May 8
  - Fall Headshots by Bill Ziskin Photography: Volleyball, Men's Soccer, and Staff, 2013 August 15
  - Winter Headshots by Bill Ziskin, 2013 September
  - Winter Sports Headshots, 2013 September
  - Men's Basketball Champions, 2014 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Spring Athlete Headshots by Bill Ziskin, 2014 February
  - Athlete Headshots by Bill Ziskin Photography, 2015 February
  - Men's Lacrosse Headshots by Bill Ziskin Photography, 2015 February
  - Women's Lacrosse Headshots by Bill Ziskin Photography, 2015 February
  - Headshots by Bill Ziskin, 2015 February
  - Headshots by Bill Ziskin: Men's Lacrosse, 2015 February
  - Headshots by Bill Ziskin: Women's Lacrosse, 2015 February
  - Football Posters, 2015 September-2015 October (Oversized 1)
  - Men's Soccer Senior Night, 2015 October 24
  - Men's Soccer Match v. Western Michigan University, Kalamazoo, Michigan, 2017 November 19
  - Andre Duncan, Tom McGoldrick, Kelly Paolino, Kenny Ozhal, Matt Caliandro, Undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Assistant Trainer Colleen O'Donnell, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Athlete Headshot Negatives, Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Athlete Headshots, Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Athlete Headshots, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Athlete Headshots, Contact Sheets and Negatives, Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Athletics Staff ( 1 of 2), Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Athletics Staff ( 1 of 2), Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Athletics Staff Headshots and Logo, Undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Athletics Team Gathering, Featuring Bob Ford, Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Athletics Trip Photo, Undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Baseball and Tennis Headshots, Undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Baseball Crowds, Undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - basketball Negative, Undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Basketball Team, Undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Basketball: Adam Ursprung, Undated
  - Basketball: Barry Cavanaugh, Undated
  - Basketball: Danny Croutier, Undated
  - Basketball: Don Cohen, Undated
  - Basketball: Garry Murray, Undated
  - Basketball: Gary Trevett, Undated
  - Basketball: Jason Graber, Undated
  - Basketball: Jim Oppedisano, Undated
  - Basketball: John Dieckelman, Undated
  - Basketball: Michael Shene, Undated
  - Basketball: Mike Cinque, Undated
  - Basketball: Todd Cetnar, Undated
  - Bill Moore, Negative, Undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Bill Ziskin, Photography, UAlbany Athletes, New York Giants, Undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Bob Ewell Photography, Damien the Great Dane, Undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Brian DePasquale, Negatives, Undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Brian DePasquale, Photography, Undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Brian DePasquale, Phys Ed 339 [cd], Undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Bud light Daredevil Mark Odgers, Undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Campus, Undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Campus Aerial Shots, Undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Campus, Football, Basketball and Gym Photographs, Slides and Negatives, Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Cheerleading, Undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Coaches, Contact Sheet and Negatives, Undated (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Columbia University Men's Basketball Alumni Reception, Undated (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Female Tennis Player Contact Sheet, Undated (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Field Hockey. Angie Stegel, Undated (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Football, Undated (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Football, Undated (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Football Action, Undated (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Football Helmet Logo with Logo Sheets, Undated (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Football Jersey Number 96, Undated (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Football Misc., Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Football Misc., Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Football Proofs, Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Football Shots Colographics ( 1 of 2), Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Football Shots Colographics ( 2 of 2), Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Football Staff, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Football Staff and Team, Undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Football Team, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Football Teams, Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Football, Andy Shein, Undated (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Football, Artie Arroyo, Undated (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Football, Brian Miesegaes, Undated (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Football, Chad Hotaling, Undated (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Football, Charles Helly, Undated (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Football, Chris Locci, Undated (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Football, Chris Robertson, Undated (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Football, Dachry Simpson, Undated (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Football, Ed Richard, Undated (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Football, Eddie Loren Williams, Undated (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Football, J.T. Herfurth, Undated (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Football, Jay Rosenberg, Undated (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Football, Jeffrey D. Emerson, Undated (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Football, Jermey Kackjian, Undated (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Football, Joe Carello, Undated (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Football, Jon Isernia, Undated (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Football, Matt Bass, Undated (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Football, Nick Cremona, Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Football, Todd Wangler, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Football, Vic Freeman, Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Headshots, Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Headshots - Negatives, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Headshots, Digital, Undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Individual at Football Stadium, Negatives, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Lee McElroy, Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Men's Lacrosse Team, Undated (Oversized 1)
  - Men's Lacrosse v. Siena, Undated (Oversized 1)
  - Men's and Women's Athlete Headshot Negatives, Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball Contact Sheet, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Men's Basketball Head Coach Richard "Doc" Savers, Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Men's Basketball Negatives, Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)